

# Jason Rostar

Web Developer, Programmer, & Designer

Military Veteran with an inactive Secret Security Clearance and over 9 years of proven experience in the United States Navy. Accomplished measurable results while leading teams in a dynamic, fast - paced environment. Possess a comprehensive background in full stack web development and administration, and creative problem solving derived from conducting domestic and global operations in multiple countries worldwide. Recipient of multiple awards for outstanding performance and professionalism. Career supported by the active pursuit of Lambda School Full Stack Web Development program.

$\times$	jason.rostar@yahoo.com		541-226-6367
9	Grants Pass, OR		www.jasonrostar.net
in	linkedin.com/in/jasonrostarcmu	()	github.com/JasonRostar

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

JavaScript/HTML5/CSS3 SCSS/LESS/Material UI Node/Express/Knex Unit and Integration Testing

ReactJS/Redux/Context SQL/SQLite/MySQL Python/CS Version Control / Git

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **United States Navy**

Aviation Maintenance Administration

02/2010 - 05/2016 Various Locations

- Utilized database administration knowledge by maintaining server and database security and data integrity, creating and managing user log-in accounts, managing hardware and software upgrades, which resulted in over 1000 mishap-free flight hours during deployments.
- Implemented and administered Local Area Networks (LAN) aboard U.S. Navy ships to support maintenance and flight operations contributing to the mission success of two West Pacific deployments.
- Managed an inventory of over 500 items; accurate accounting and upkeep resulted in the saving of over \$1M in maintenance costs for the Navy.

#### **United States Navy**

#### Security Team Lead / Correctional Officer

06/2016 - 05/2019

- Lead Petty Officer of Miramar Brig Security Team, comprised of five Soldiers and Marines, responsible for providing a safe working environment for the installation of over 8 million dollars in state-of-the-art security cameras and touch-screen monitors.
- Received a Navy Marine Corps Achievement Medal for outstanding service over the 3 year period working at the Miramar, California Brig.
- Actively pursued bachelors degree from Central Michigan University and Department of Labor office management certificate.

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor of Science (B.S.) degree - Organizational and Business Administration

Central Michigan University, Mount Pleasant, Mi

08/2019

- Formally educated in skills pertaining to the legal environment of business, communication, public relations, human resources, organizational psychology, and management through best practices.

# **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

https://github.com/JasonRostar (08/2016 - Present)

- Regularly updated with new projects created with tools such as

#### **CERTIFICATES**

Oracle 11g Database - Syracuse University (04/2019)

Perform complex, hands-on activities through labs, study and practice with SQL, SQL Developer and Relational Databases.

Certificate of Completion of Apprenticeship (06/2017) Plan, organize, implement, and control organizational activities. Schedule work

Office Manager/Administrative Services - Department of Labor -

assignments; organize the flow of work.

Computer Operator - Department of Labor - Certificate of Completion of Apprenticeship (12/2014)

Maintain back-ups of computer systems utilizing external sources. Train users in the proper operation of computers and use of associated devices.